export const scienceQuestions = [
    {id: 1, question: "What is the name of the galaxy we are in?", answer: "The Milky Way", points: 100, answered: false},
    {id: 2, question: "Who is responsible for the saying 'What comes up, must come down'?", answer: "Sir Isaac Newton", points: 400, answered: false},
    {id: 3, question: "What makes up 71% of Earth?", answer: "Water", points: 100, answered: false},
    {id: 4, question: "When it comes to the human body, what is the largest organ?", answer: "The skin", points: 100, answered: false},
    {id: 5, question: "What is the chemical symbol for gold?", answer: "Au", points: 300, answered: false},
    {id: 6, question: "What are the 3 common states of matter?", answer: "Solid, liquid, and gas", points: 100, answered: false},
    {id: 7, question: "What type of energy is stored when an elastic band is stretched?", answer: "Potential energy", points: 200, answered: false},
    {id: 8, question: "What is the common name for deoxyribonucleic acid?", answer: "DNA", points: 200, answered: false},
    {id: 9, question: "What event is responsible for the creation of all the matter in the universe?", answer: "The Big Bang", points: 200, answered: false},
    {id: 10, question: "At what temperaure are Celsius and Fahrenheit equal?", answer: "-40 degrees", points: 400, answered: false},
    {id: 11, question: "What is the only metal that is a liquid at room temperature?", answer: "Mercury", points: 300, answered: false},
    {id: 12, question: "What is the center of an atom called?", answer: "Nucleus", points: 200, answered: false},
    {id: 13, question: "What is the term for a group of organisms that cna interbreed and produce fertile offspring?", answer: "Species", points: 300, answered: false},
    {id: 14, question: "What organ is reponsible for producing insulin? answer?", answer: "The Pancreas", points: 400, answered: false},
    {id: 15, question: "How many bones are present in the human body?", answer: "206", points: 300, answered: false},
    {id: 16, question: "What is the most abundant gas in Earth's atmosphone?", answer: "Nitrogen", points: 400, answered: false}
]